smart-traffic.co.uk 2017-09-09

# Bigg

  Bigg​.
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy outlines how Smart Traffic T/A Bigg uses and protects any information that you
provide Smart Traffic T/A Bigg during your visit to this website.
We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. You can be assured that any
information from which you can be identified that you provide us when using this website will only
be used with accordance with this privacy statement.
Smart Traffic T/A Bigg may change this policy periodically by updating this page. For this reason we
advise that you visit this page from time to time to ensure you are happy with any changes. This
updated policy is effective from January 2015.
What we collect.
We do not collect personally identifiable information about visitors to the website.
The only time we might collect this information is if you decide to email us or complete a contact
form that is on the website. Your information will be treated with the utmost confidence and will
never be shared or published.
What we do with the information we gather.
If you fill out a contact form or email Smart Traffic T/A Bigg, we may contact you in response to
your message or subsequently in the future. This may include promotional emails about special
offers, new products, the latest in industry news or other information which we think you might
find interesting using the email address that you have provided.
Occasionally, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. This
may be through email, phone or mail.
You can prevent this information by contact us using the fields on the contact forms on this
website and requesting that all such communication stops.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised
access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures
to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

  Bigg​.
About Cookies
A cookie is an American term for biscuit – It is also a small file which is placed onto your computer
or device and can be used for a number of purposes, including enabling website functionality,
analysing website usage or targeting advertising and tracking campaign performance.
A cookie does not give us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the
data you choose to share with us if you fill in a contact form or email us.
You have the ability and choice to accept or decline cookies and delete existing ones. Most web
browsers automatically accept cookies but you can modify the browser settings to decline cookies
if you prefer. The help section of your chosen browser or its accompanying website will provide
instructions on how to accept, decline and delete cookies.
Declining cookies may prevent you from using all the features on our website, as some
functionality may not work.
How we use cookies
On the Smart Traffic T/A Bigg website, we use Google Analytics cookies are used to a) analyse how
our website is used – for example the volume of visitors to the site or specific pages and b) analyse
how visitors found the website – for example reviewing searches that led to a site visitor, and which
traffic sources led to a contact form being completed or an email sent. We will access this
information on your first visit to our website and may access it again on subsequent visits.
You can read more about Google Analytics cookies on the Google site and download a browser
plugin to enable you to opt out of Google Analytics cookies on any websites.
Future designs of this website will be made in concordance with the Privacy and Electronic
Communications Regulations 2011.
Links to other websites.
Our website contains links to other websites of interest. However once you have used these links to
leave our site it is important to note that we do not have any control over that website. Therefore,
we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide whilst
visiting these sites and this privacy statement does not govern such sites. We advise that you
exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You have the right to request details of personal information which we hold about you under the
Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be applicable. If you would like a copy of the information
held on you please contact us.
